http://www.infonancial.com/privacy

Homeproductscore bankingdigital bankingloan origination systemapi & interfacesServicesTechnologyCYbersecurityATM/POS SecurityaboutnewsContact usINFONANCIAL PRIVACYPrivacy PolicyWe are committed to protecting your privacy and keeping you informed of how your personal information is used. This Privacy Policy applies to personal data we collect through the INFONANCIAL.com website, and other websites which we operate and on which we post a link to this policy. We will only collect and use your personal information in accordance with the current Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA). Have questions concerning collected data and privacy? Please contact us:info@infonancial.comPersonal DataBy using the INFONANCIAL website and its subdomains, you consent to the collection, retention and use of your personal information in accordance with the terms of this policy. We only collect personal information from you if you interact with us through our websites when you for example fill out a contact form, send us an email, create a user account, purchase/register a product or service, request support, or apply for a job.We use this information provided by you only for our own business purposes, and will never disclose it to third parties, whether for commercial or non-commercial purposes. We protect your personal information with appropriate safeguards.Use of data when registering for the email newsletterIf you are a registered user of a INFONANCIAL newsletter and have supplied your email address, INFONANCIAL may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, new services, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with INFONANCIAL and our products. We do anonymize your interaction with our newsletter. If you subsequently wish to opt out you can do so by clicking the unsubscribe link in our newsletter emails or you can contact us at the address above. This information will not be disclosed to third parties.Log DataGenerally, you may use our website without disclosing your identity and personal data. What we collect is the information that your browser sends whenever you visit our website (log data). The data collected includes for example:Referrer (page from which our website was accessed)Search terms (if a search engine was the referrer)IP is anonymous but evaluated to determine the country of origin and the providerBrowser, operating system, installed plug-ins and screen resolutionTime spent on the websitePublic Forum ReminderINFONANCIAL subdomains include a wiki, a customer portal, and mailing lists which are available to users. These are public areas so please remember that any information that is disclosed there becomes public. Think twice before disclosing your personal data or your company data there if you don't wont them to become public.CookiesOur website uses cookies. A cookie is a small data file sent to your browser and stored on your device. Most of the cookies we use are session cookies and will be deleted after the end of your browser session; some are persistent for a certain amount of time and allow to recognize your browser within the next session (for example if you choose the “remember me” sign in preference).You can change your browser settings to restrict or block some or all cookies. Check the information provided in your browser’s help section for specific instructions on how to manage cookies. Opting out or blocking some cookies may affect the functionality of the website (such as the remember preferences).HomeProductsServicesAboutNewsContact UsPrivacy PolicyCareersCopyright © 2020 INFONANCIAL Solutions. All rights reserved.
